[Adapted from Che Ye Liu Xiang's
novel of the same name]
[Episode 9]
Fan Fan.
It's been two months.
I want congee.
Pork congee?
Don't add chopped spring onions.
If I don't add spring onions,
it'll be too gamey.
Then just add more shredded ginger.
I'll chop some celery for you instead.
The heat on the left
and right burners is different.
The right one is for making soup.
The soup pot is on the right, too.
This place...
How is it exactly like the house in Yunjing?
Big Bro.
You don't have to enter the kitchen anymore.
Just leave it to me.
- What's wrong?
- No, it's nothing.
Why are you so clumsy?
Back in Yunjing,
you always bumped into this cabinet, too.
Yeah.
This place...
is exactly like Yunjing.
I asked Lin Zi Yang
to help me with the renovation.
He's so careless.
When the time comes,
get your brother
and Lin Zi Yang out for dinner.
I'll make him apologize.
Big Bro.
Where did you get this videotape?
Look at the clarity.
Does it look like a videotape?
It's much clearer
than the ones in the video halls.
Watching "The Bride with White Hair" again?
How many times have you watched this movie?
I don't remember.
Probably many times.
What exactly is this movie about?
It's about Zhuo Yi Hang,
a disciple of a prestigious sect,
falling in love with the witch Lian Ni Shang.
Can you make my white hair turn black again?
What she meant by that was...
Can spilled water...
ever be gathered back?
It's not that Lian Ni Shang
didn't love Zhuo Yi Hang.
She couldn't come freely,
but she could leave freely.
If you like watching movies so much,
then move in with me.
As for Xiao Ping's job,
I'll leave it in your hands, Mr. Lu.
Don't be so formal, Mr. Lin.
It's my honor that you thought of me for help.
Here.
Cheers.
Well then, let's leave it to Shen Zhi Qin.
Let me introduce you. This is Shen Zhi Qin.
The best trader in the futures market.
Hand Xiao Ping over to him.
I'll give him a strict order.
He must train Xiao Ping to be an expert.
The name Shen Zhi Qin...
sounds like someone who gets things done.
I'm just an ordinary citizen.
I have to be diligent to survive.
He's just like that.
He has character.
I like it.
Mr. Lu, this toast is for you, too.
Thank you for the job opportunity.
Zi Yang, we're both straightforward people.
Let's not play games.
I'm not doing this to do you a favor.
It's purely to please the big lord behind you.
This is a partnership.
It's not about who's pleasing whom.
Lv Qing will be here soon.
Mr. Lu, I'm finished eating.
If there's nothing else, I'll head out.
Xiao Ping, be at the office
at 9:00 A.M. tomorrow.
You'll be following me from now on.
Don't take it personally.
He's just like that by nature.
He's gone dull from watching the market.
Come.
But... he's even so arrogant
toward you, Mr. Lu.
The man truly has talent.
- If he's arrogant, so be it.
- That won't do.
No matter how capable he is,
can he beat you, Mr. Lu?
You're far too gracious.
If a person has real talent,
what does that have to do with being social?
Hey, Lv Qing.
Drink up as a penalty!
Lv Qing.
We haven't seen each other for years.
Isn't it because you're so busy, Mr. Lu?
Look at what you're saying.
Zi Yang knows how many times
I've invited you out.
But you've been ignoring me.
Well, I'm here to take my penalty.
Lv Qing, I didn't mean to blame you.
I just have this one bad habit.
I'm overly attentive.
I almost scared Xiao Fan
into closing his account with me.
Mr. Lu, you're being too modest.
Aren't you just scaring our Xiao Fan?
Look at that. He just got here,
and he's already defending his own.
Big Bro, why are you here?
They're here for me. How could I not come?
Are you really letting my brother do this?
I'm afraid of causing you trouble.
It's fine.
By the way,
the CSRC might issue
new regulations next quarter
to regulate the securities market.
It's only a matter of time.
It's not a question of if, but when.
Whether the CSRC regulates it or not,
won't you still make a fortune, Mr. Lu?
I still need everyone's support.
Right? Come on, cheers.
Cheers.
[Textile Bureau]
Big Bro, you should head out first.
Your car is too conspicuous.
Look at you now.
Good morning, Ms. Xu.
You're a dark horse, Fan Fan.
You even have a private car now.
And this is...
This is my brother.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Fan Fan mentions you all the time.
He said you're a publicity officer
at the Textile Bureau.
A real wordsmith.
A great talent. Impressive.
He's my brother-in-law.
I know everything about Fan Fan.
Isn't he just waiting for a divorce?
Big Bro.
I have to pick up the plan sheet this morning.
I'll get going now.
Let's go, Ms. Xu.
I want fish congee tomorrow morning.
Big Bro, how about I make it on the weekend?
I've been working the morning shift lately.
Actually, you don't have to come.
I'll make the congee every morning
and bring it to you.
Whatever.
Big Bro, if there's nothing else,
I'll head out.
Is there anything you want me to buy for you?
Or something you need me to get?
Should I help make a spare key?
You want to give me a key?
Big Bro, there's no need.
I'm always available. No need for a key.
Lu Xiao Fan.
Don't think your ass is that valuable.
Then... I'll bring the congee tomorrow morning.
If you dare to leave today,
don't bother coming back tomorrow.
Then I... I'll move in this weekend.
Wait.
Big Bro, this...
If you ever throw this in the trash again,
I'll throw you in there, too.
Fan Fan, are you moving in for good?
It's more convenient to move there.
This place is a bit small.
It'll be more comfortable
for you and Ping Ping.
Then thank Lv Qing for me.
Behave yourself when you're there.
Don't cause trouble for Lv Qing.
Oh, Lv Qing loves congee.
Can you make it? Or should I go make it?
No need, Mom.
This congee is quite a hassle.
You don't know the recipe.
Lv Qing is such a good child.
He's never made us feel awkward
and helps us out in every way.
- He really is...
- Mom.
Warm up the food.
Eat, eat, eat. All you know is eating.
Your brother finally came home for once.
Isn't talking more important than eating?
Once you warm it up, we can eat together.
Fan Fan, stay for dinner before you go.
Xiao Fan.
Do you know how much money was made
after Bei Lv Qing opened that account?
I don't care about those things.
Do you know how much that one trade made?
1.6 million, Xiao Fan!
My monthly salary is only 2,000 yuan.
That's only 25,000 a year.
I'd have to work myself to the bone
for 70 years to earn that much.
He got it in the blink of an eye.
How do you know about Lv Qing's trades?
His trades are all handled by Shen Zhi Qin.
Yeah.
I took a peek while he was in the bathroom.
Why did you peek at his account?
What's the big deal?
You talk about the Bei family
like they're pure saints.
But after all is said and done,
they just won't let us in on the money.
Lu Xiao Ping, can you just stop for once?
Ping Ping.
Fan Fan, let's eat first.
No thanks. Lv Qing is waiting
for me downstairs.
Fan Fan.
Fan Fan!
I know.
Your brother really is a hopeless case.
But he's still family, after all.
Mom.
I can't make the decisions on this.
Fan Fan, take care of yourself.
Is your mother doing okay?
She's fine.
She misses you a lot.
She even said
she wanted to make congee for you herself.
She thinks mine isn't good enough.
When should we bring her over?
I'll take her around to see the sights.
If she comes here,
she'd probably have no peace
because of your brother.
Mr. Shen, are you watching the market?
This is a real eye-opener for me.
No wonder so many people
are sucking up to my brother.
So, that's how it is.
Thanks for the hard work.
You all did well today.
Don't just stare at the screens all day.
Go to the VIP room more often
and listen for news.
Who knows who will be the boss in the future?
Why is it you again?
Do you have a problem with that?
Where's Li Wen Xi?
We broke up.
Broke up?
Didn't you notice I haven't been
wearing my ring lately?
I didn't want to overthink it.
Hey, Bei Lv Qing.
Are you still there?
Let's talk business.
No wonder when I asked Li Wen Xi
to collaborate the other day,
he turned me down so flatly.
How about I act as a bridge
and introduce you two?
Enough. Let's talk business.
It's good if Li Wen Xi is willing to cooperate,
but if he isn't, there's no need to force it.
Right?
We don't need him.
But if he's intent on sabotaging us,
that would be quite troublesome.
Why would I be afraid of him sabotaging me?
Exactly.
Don't forget,
no matter how capable the Li family is,
that's in Hong Kong.
This is our home turf.
Playing here, he has to follow our lead.
But Li Wen Xi has deep pockets.
He has his family's backing.
If he really starts dumping positions,
we might not necessarily be his match.
The Chinese stock market is plummeting.
From over 1,000 points to just over 300.
It is akin to a cliff dive.
A total freefall.
That has been the general trend.
This is our first battle.
The elders are all watching.
We set the policies.
We built the market.
If this were in Hong Kong,
I wouldn't be so sure.
But here, does Li Wen Xi even know how to play?
He's just an outsider.
What do you think of this place?
It's... It's very nice.
I'll find a way to transfer
to Austria next year.
I'll settle down there.
You're coming with me.
Bei Lv Qing, can't you be more serious?
Don't worry about the funds.
The money will be
in your account tomorrow morning.
Our accounts must be separate.
There can't be any visible connection.
I've already handled all of that.
As expected of Mr. Bei. Reliable.
Sell them all.
Wh-What?
Are you trading stocks?
Sell them tomorrow.
You're not suited for the financial market.
With the little money you have,
just put your salary into a fixed-term deposit.
This is my secondary card.
You don't need to ask me
when you want to use it.
Big Bro.
Aren't you...
afraid I'll spend until you're bankrupt?
You are mine.
The things you buy are mine, too.
How could I go bankrupt?
Big Bro.
I haven't showered yet, Big Bro.
If you dare to provoke me,
you'll have to pay the price.
I... I haven't finished the apple.
The top has been eaten,
but the bottom's waiting.
We share the bitter and the sweet.
Big Bro.
- Fan Fan.
- Big Bro.
- It's me, Fan Fan.
Someone's here.
- Someone's really here.
- Fan Fan.
Fan Fan.
It's me, Fan Fan.
Brother?
Why are you here?
You've already eaten?
Take it.
You have no situational awareness at all.
Why did you buy this?
Look at what you're saying.
I'm here to thank Lv Qing for finding me a job.
How could I come empty-handed?
You don't understand social etiquette at all.
Look at this decor. It's really nice.
It looks very relaxing.
What style is this again?
Mediterranean.
- Hey, Lv Qing.
- Big Bro.
Have you eaten?
Didn't Xiao Fan just tell you?
Lv Qing.
I'm here to thank you.
No need.
Just thank your brother.
Yes, yes.
Ultimately, I know...
Lv Qing, you only helped me because
of the relationship between our families.
Otherwise, how could a man of your status
bother with the affairs of commoners like us?
Go cut some fruit for Lv Qing.
Why are you just sitting here?
No need. I just ate.
Actually, I've wanted to come for a long time.
But...
I haven't achieved much at work yet.
I was afraid I'd embarrass you, so...
I was too ashamed to come.
Lv Qing...
Since you're such a wise person,
I won't beat around the bush with you.
I know you're a big client at Langjian.
I just wanted to ask if you could...
let me be your trader.
Big Bro!
Shen Zhi Qin is the top trader at Langjian.
You're a rookie. How can you compare?
We're family, let's be honest.
I am a rookie, that's true.
But is Shen Zhi Qin
as reliable as one of your own?
Who knows what kind of shady business
he's doing behind your back.
- Right?
- This is non-negotiable.
Bro! Can't you just do your job properly?
Xiao Fan.
Why are you interrupting adults?
I just want to work faithfully
for my own people.
Let me put it this way.
Shen Zhi Qin seems trustworthy.
But the more flawless a person seems,
the bigger their hidden flaws are.
Shen Zhi Qin watches the market all day.
He doesn't say more than
three sentences to anyone.
Don't you think this kind of trader
is a little too perfect?
Fine.
Big Bro!
- He doesn't know anything.
- What do I need to know?
I'll just follow wherever Lv Qing points.
Besides, Lv Qing has
so much inside information.
How could I lose money?
Enough.
I have things to do.
You two brothers can talk.
I'll leave you to it, Big Bro.
Look at you, following him around
every single day.
Cooking and serving tea.
You're acting like a maid.
What have you gained from it?
Fine, I know how you are.
Don't worry.
When I strike it rich,
I definitely won't forget my little brother.
I'm tired today.
I'm going back now.
Think about what I told you.
Big Bro, what were you doing last night?
I didn't even notice when you got back.
Do I have to report everything I do to you now?
That's not what I meant.
Come and eat.
Big Bro.
You really don't have to mind Lu Xiao Ping.
No matter what he says to you,
don't agree to it.
Wouldn't that be more troublesome?
You people from the Lu family
never give up until you get what you want.
If he wants to do it, let him.
Why did you come to see me during work?
Did you get into trouble?
Can't you wish your brother well?
It's really nothing?
I got my first paycheck today.
Guess how much it is.
Over 10,000 yuan.
Then work hard.
Keep your feet on the ground.
Which one of us is the older brother?
If there's nothing else,
I'm going back to work.
Look at you...
Actually, there is something.
What do you want?
The Ministry of Agriculture will release
some big news in the next few months.
It's top secret.
Bei Lv Qing and his people
must have known the details long ago.
Lu Tao is following him so closely.
He definitely wants to hitch a ride.
Just keep a close eye
on the market for Big Bro.
Don't worry about anything else.
Everyone wants to get in on such a big deal.
Can't you keep your ears open?
You might not want in, but your brother does.
It takes 300,000 to open an account.
Where would you get that much money?
Why worry about that?
You're such a blockhead.
I can't get through to you.
What's wrong?
Is something the matter?
Actually, it's nothing.
I can tell when something's on your mind.
Is my brother doing... all right at work?
You don't have to worry about his affairs.
I'm just afraid he'll cause you trouble.
I'm not even worried about that.
- Is your brother in?
- Yeah.
Eating so early?
Have something on later?
What's up?
The great Mr. Lin
doesn't usually drop by for a visit.
Fine, fine. I shouldn't have teased you.
Let's talk business.